

GUIDO CALCIANO

PROFILE

I've been working with human groups and teams of professionals for the last 10 years. Communication, flexibility and looking for consensus are an essential part of my formation. In the last years I've taken my first steps into IT, and I keep on learning every day. Currently I'm looking for an exciting new project. Contact me for any questions!

RECENT PROJECTS

Portfolio

<u>https://guidocalciano.com.ar</u>

Google Clone: Google, Youtube and Image Search API. React *

Take note!: Write, edit and del your notes. React *



Cinema Website: Register and login, search, favs. React 🕸

CONTACT

(+549) 11 5732 4784

CABA, Buenos Aires, Argentina

(7) /guidocano

in /guidocalciano

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web Developer

Freelance. Jan 2022 - Present

Creating webpage layouts, styling, writing code, editing content, SEO optimization, mantainance, and making adjustments based on client feedback.

IT Apprenticeship Program

Sabio School of Software Engineering - USA. Mar 2022 - Jun 2022 At Sabio I learnt to work in an Agile environment and successfully teached other students basic notions of programming while improved my technical english.

Special Education Teacher

Adeei. Mar 2014 - Dic 2021

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Codo a Codo 4.0 - React.js - GO

Buenos Aires City Government. Aug 2022 - In progress

Modern React with Redux

Udemy, by Stephen Grider. Jun 2022

React.is

Sabio School of Software Engineering. Apr 2022

REST Client and Ajax

Sabio School of Software Engineering. Mar 2022

¡Query and JavaScript Fundamentals

Sabio School of Software Engineering. Feb 2022

Codo a Codo 4.0 - Fullstack Python

Buenos Aires City Government. Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

EDUCATION

Higher Technician in Web Development and **Digital Apps**

ISPC. Mar 2022 - In progress

Bachelor's Degree in Psychology

Buenos Aires University. Mar 2006 - Dec 2012

SKILLS

TECHNOLOGIES

REACT.JS

SQL

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

PYTHON

BOOTSTRAP

JQUERY

AJAX

GIT

LANGUAGES

• English: bilingual

· Spanish: native

SOFT SKILLS

PROBLEM-SOLVER ADAPTABILITY

OPEN-MINDEDNESS

COMMUNICATION CREATIVITY

TEAMWORK